{
    "id": "7afc6963d1664aaf84f587d53672fa3f",
    "title": "Sentence Completion Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "Your sister is ………………… nuisance.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "quite",
                "quite a"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "919e028b3ce1489e8653acf5fde713d6"
        },
        {
            "question": "She was …………………. annoyed to find him in her room.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "very",
                "very much"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "54e2f1dbeab048e2ab41b9a0bd0b1904"
        },
        {
            "question": "It is ……………… cold.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "too",
                "too much"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "39c6ef12e7d64d1bb664b590723f9f1b"
        },
        {
            "question": "It is very cold – you ……………….. take a coat.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "have better",
                "had better"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "b369489d78e9400c86254b90ad5a3537"
        },
        {
            "question": "He is ………………. imaginative.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "little",
                "not very"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "98313494376d43219071d463f6da3f75"
        },
        {
            "question": "…………………. a painter are you?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "How much",
                "How much of"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "59ea56ab3e1f493eb947e6d1c2cf9d53"
        },
        {
            "question": "I think she is ………………… a fool.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "a bit",
                "a bit of"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "0adde1b59e024422bec07839c3cd5a9e"
        },
        {
            "question": "It was ………………… informal get-together than a meeting.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "more a",
                "more of",
                "more of an"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "9af8bf78d0cc4af4a4464a9d26d8aca6"
        },
        {
            "question": "You have been ………………..!",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "such help",
                "such a help!"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "85581a1f4f194c1c9325b79bd1ea5f59"
        },
        {
            "question": "Stop talking ………………….",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "such nonsense",
                "such a nonsense"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "240ef5f3211345028a7b18bd9e212705"
        }
    ]
}